export const myQuestions = {
    "pheobeQuestions": [{
            question: "After Phoebe misses out on the London trip, where does the group try and plan a trip to?",
            answers: {
                a: "Atlantic City",
                b: "New Jersey",
                c: "The Hamptons",
                d: "Brooklyn",
            },
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "Why do Phoebe and Mike break up?",
            answers: {
                a: "His parents do not apporve",
                b: "He is allergic to cats",
                c: "He never wants to get married",
                d: "She wants to go back to David",
            },
            correctAnswer: "C",

        },
        {
            question: "Which TV Network Did Phoebe Hate?",
            answers: {
                a: "PBS",
                b: "CNN",
                c: "BBC",
                d: "ITV",
            },
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "How Much Money Did Phoebe Get After Finding A Thumb In Her Soda?",
            answers: {
                a: "$2000",
                b: "$3000",
                c: "$5000",
                d: "$7000",
            },
            correctAnswer: "D",
        }
    ],
    "joeyQuestions": [{
            question: "What's the name of Joey's imaginary friend?",
            a: "Chris",
            b: "Matt",
            c: "Maurice",
            d: "Jeff",
            correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
            question: "When he turned 30, Joey cried like a baby. He cried again at the 30th birthday celebrations of some of the other friends. Who were they?",
            a: "Chandler and Rachel",
            b: "Ross and Rachel",
            c: "Chandler and Pheobe",
            d: "Ross and Monica",
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the name of Joey's stuffed penguin pal?",
            a: "Cuddly",
            b: "Sleepy",
            c: "Kissy",
            d: "Hugsy",
            correctAnswer: "D",
        },
        {
            question: "What was Joey's last line on the show?",
            a: "Shall we get coffee?",
            b: "Sure, where?",
            c: "I guess so",
            d: "I'm hungry",
            correctAnswer: "B",
        },
    ],
    "rachelQuestions": [{
            question: "Who Did Rachel Almost Marry?",
            a: "Harry",
            b: "Barry",
            c: "Jerry",
            d: "Perry",
            correctAnswer: "B",
        }, {
            question: "How Long Was The Letter She Wrote For Ross?",
            a: "18 pages, front and back",
            b: "15 pages, front and back",
            c: "19 pages, front and back",
            d: "13 pages, front and back",
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "What Weird Fear Did Rachel Have?",
            a: "things touching her feet",
            b: "things touching her knees",
            c: "things touching her elbows",
            d: "things touching her hair",
            correctAnswer: "D",
        },
        {
            question: "What Pet Did Rachel Buy That Freaked Everyone Out?",
            a: "A rat",
            b: "A snake",
            c: "A hairless cat",
            d: "A ferret",
            correctAnswer: "C",
        },
    ],
    "rossQuestions": [{
            question: "What Was The Name Of The Student Ross Dated In Season 6?",
            a: "Annabelle",
            b: "Isabelle",
            c: "Elizabeth",
            d: "Eliza",
            correctAnswer: "C",
        }, {
            question: "How Many Times Has Ross Been Divorced?",
            a: "2",
            b: "3",
            c: "4",
            d: "5",
            correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
            question: "What Was The Surname Of Emily, Ross' Second Wife?",
            a: "Wheeler",
            b: "Wilson",
            c: "Willis",
            d: "Waltham",
            correctAnswer: "D",
        },
        {
            question: "What Was The Name Of The Band Chandler And Ross Formed In High School?",
            a: "Way, No way",
            b: "Way, Yes way",
            c: "Way, There is a way",
            d: "Way, Some way",
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
    ],
    "monicaQuestions": [{
            question: "What Are The Name's Of Monica's Parents?",
            a: "Judy and Jack",
            b: "Judy and Joseph",
            c: "Jill and Jack",
            d: "Janet and Jim",
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "Who Lived With Monica Before Rachel?",
            a: "Ross",
            b: "Chandler",
            c: "Joey",
            d: "Pheobe",
            correctAnswer: "D",
        },
        {
            question: "What Did Monica's Parents Spend Her Wedding Fund On?",
            a: "Car",
            b: "Beach house",
            c: "Cruise",
            d: "Starting a new business",
            correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
            question: "What Did Monica And Chandler Name Their Twins?",
            a: "Jack and Jill",
            b: "Eric and Jaqoline",
            c: "Jack and Erica",
            d: "Eric and Joshephine",
            correctAnswer: "C",
        },
    ],
    "chandlerQuestions": [{
            question: "What Is Chandler's Middle Name?",
            a: "Maura",
            b: "Muriel",
            c: "Mary",
            d: "Marybeth",
            correctAnswer: "B",
        },
        {
            question: "Who Does Chandler's Online Date Turn Out To Be?",
            a: "Monica",
            b: "Kathy",
            c: "Janice",
            d: "Joanna",
            correctAnswer: "C",
        },
        {
            question: "Who Does Chandler Realise He Has A Lot In Common With?",
            a: "Mr Heckles",
            b: "Treeger",
            c: "Richard",
            d: "Pete",
            correctAnswer: "A",
        },
        {
            question: "Who Did Chandler Get Trapped In An ATM Vestibule With?",
            a: "Cindy Crawford",
            b: "Winona Ryder",
            c: "Yasmine Bleeth",
            d: "Jill Goodacre",
            correctAnswer: "D",
        },
    ],
}